Guide to The Peter Dougherty Collection 1965 - 2001 MSS.213
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Sound recordings, 242013
  - Subseries A: Audio Works, 1976-1985; 197226
    - Television, Bottom Line June 11, 1978 early show, Pistols Jan 14 1978, ID: 213.0199; 198231 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0199, Case 213.0199_pt.1, Case 213.0199_pt.2)
      Side B: Knockin, Marquee Moon, See No Evil (encore), Satisfaction (encore), No Feelings, Problems
    - Television 8 April 2001/ Camber Sands -A.T.P., ID: 213.0200; 198232 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0200, Case 213.0200_pt.1, Case 213.0200_pt.2)
    - Television/ Live June 15th 1975 CBGB, ID: 213.0201; 198233 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0201, Case 213.0201_pt.1, Case 213.0201_pt.2)
      Side A: Fire Engine, Prove it, Poor Circulation, Friction, Breakin My Heart, Shirts, Surprise Package, Mr Blues
      Side B: I Don't Care, Venus de Milo 95, Little Johnny Jewel 225, Foxhole 360, Marquee Moon 490, Double Exposure
      Container annotation: TV-guitar, vocal. Richard Lloyd, guitar. Billy Fecca-drums. Fred Smith-bass.
    - Television - My Father's Place, May 24, 1976, ID: 213.0202; 198234 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0202, Case 213.0202_pt.1, Case 213.0202_pt.2)
      Side A: See No Evil (Sound check), I Don't Care (Sound check), See No Evil, Prove It, Let Me Out, Friction, I Don't Care, Knockin on Heaven's Door, Marquee Moon [Door]
      Side B: 7. cont'd, 8. Poor Circulation, 9. Venus de Milo, 10. Little Johnny Jewel, 11. Elevation, 12. Kingdom Come
      Container annotation: Recorded by Jackie E
    - Television Feb 15th 1975 CBGB, ID: 213.0203; 198247 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0203, Case 213.0203)
      Side A: Psychotic Reaction, UFO, Foxhole*, Blank Generation, Marquee Moon, Double Exposure
      Side B: Fire Engine, Prove It, Friction, Venus de Milo, Poor Circulation, Hard on Love.
      Object Annotation: Side A: Roxy Music For Your Pleasure Side B: V.U. -Loaded
    - Television June 15th 1975 CBGB 1st with Fred Smith/ August 8th 1975 RnR fest, ID: 213.0204; 198248 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0204, Case 213.0204_pt.1, Case 213.0204_pt.2)
      Side 1: Fire Engine, Prove It, Poor Circulation, Friction, Breakin in My Heart, I Don't Care*, Venus de Milo, Little Johnny Jewel*, Foxhole*
      Side 2: Marquee Moon, Double Exposure*, Fire Engine, Prove It*, Poor Circulation, Little Johnny Jewel
    - Television/ Patti Smith/ Live March 22nd 1975, March 22, 1975; ID: 213.0205; 198469 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0205, Case 213.0205)
      Side A: TELEVISION: Marquee Moon, Birds (Lloyd), Poor Circulation, Foxhole
      Side B: Hard on Love. PATTI SMITH: Captured by the Game
      Container Annotation: Patti Smith-vocals. Lenny Kaye-guitar. Richard Sohl. Ivan Kral-guitar. Property of P. Dougherty (212)5449224
    - Television/ The Mumps live Feb 22nd 1975 at CBGBs, February 22, 1975; ID: 213.0206; 198470 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0206, Case 213.0206)
      Side A (Television): Psychotic Reaction, UFO, Foxhole, Blank Generation, Marquee Moon, Double Exposure
      Side 2 (Mumps): You Gotta Be Stupid, You Should Have Seen His Face Before the Accident, Night Owl, Back on the Street, Photogenia, Muscle Boys
      Container Annotation: Richard Hell-bass. Tom Verlaine-guitar. Richard Lloyd-guitar. Billy Ficca-drums. Lance Loud-Vocal. Christain-piano. Property of P. Dougherty (212)5449224
    - Television Live Feb 22nd 1975 at CBGBs, February 22, 1975; ID: 213.0207; 198471 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0207, Case 213.0207)
      Side A: Push it or Pull it (Fire Engine), Friction, Prove it, Arms of Venus de Milo, Poor Circulation
      Side B: Hard on Love. +Roxy Music+: Out of the Blue, Thrill of it All. [swastika symbol]Hot Tuna[swastika symbol]: Come Back Baby
      Container Annotation: Rich Lloyd-v+guitar. Rich Hell-bass. Billy Ficca-drums. Tom Verlaine-vocal, guitar. Property of Peter Dougherty (212)544-9224
    - Talking Heads/ Television 8/2, undated; ID: 213.0208; 198472 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0208, Case 213.0208_pt.1, Case 213.0208_pt.2)
      Side A (Talking Heads): The Girls Wanna Be with the Girls, With Our Love, Love is Like a Building on Fire, Tentative Decisions, Psycho Killer, I'm Not in Love, Artists Only, Warning Sign
      Side B (Television): Fire Engine, Prove it, Poor Circulation, Little Johnny Jewel, Friction, Hard On Love (soft)- Kingdom Come
      Container Annotation: David Byrne- Vocal, Guitar. Tina-bass. Chris Frantz- Drums. / Television TV- Guitar, Vocal. R Lloyd- Guitar, Billy Fecca- Drums. Fred Smith - Bass
    - 1- Television March 12, 1976- Live at CBGB aith MONG, ID: 213.0209; 198473 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0209, Case 213.0209)
      Side A: Fire Engine, Venus de Milo, Torn Curtain, Little Johnny Jewel, Friction, Prove It, Knockin on Heaven's Door, Marquee Moon
      Side B: Oh Me Amore, Poor Circulation, Elevation, Let Me out
    - 2- Television: March 12, May 26, '76. Both Live at CBGB, 1976; ID: 213.0210; 198474 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0210, Case 213.0210)
      TV March 12/ May 26-
      Side A: Grip of Love, I Don't Care, Foxhole, Kingdom Come, Psychotic Reaction (encore), See No Evil, I Don't Care
      Side B: Friction, Little Johnny Jewel, Elevation, Marquee Moon
    - Television Dec 30, 1976 CBGB, December 30, 1976; ID: 213.0211; 198475 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0211, Case 213.0211)
      Side A: Fire Engine 3:30, Venus de Milo 3. Elevation 4. Little Johnny Jewel 5. I Don't Care 6. Friction 7. Marquee Moon
      Side B: See No Evil, Prove It, Adventure
    - Television July 4th 1976 Live at the Lower Manhattan Ocean Club on Chamber Street Un advertised- Strange gig- One set no breaks, July 4, 1976; ID: 213.0212; 198476 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0212)
      Side A: See No Evil, Poor Circulation, Prove it, Little Johnny Jewel, I Don't Care, Marquee Moon, Friction
      Side B: Knockin on Heaven's Door, Kingdom Come, Oh Me Amore (encore)
    - Television 4 December '92 NYC Academy, December 4, 1992; ID: 213.0213; 198477 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0213, Case 213.0213_pt.1, Case 213.0213_pt.2)
    - Television July 29, 1976 CBGB Stereo Set #1 Only, [McKim]- assistant, ID: 213.0214; 198478 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0214, Case 213.0214)
      Side A: Fire Engine, Poor Circulation, Elevation, Oh me Amore, Venus de Milo, Knockin on Heaven's Door
    - John Cale Xmas 1976/ Television Dec 27th CBGBs, ID: 213.0215; 198479 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0215, Case 213.0215_pt.1, Case 213.0215_pt.2)
      Side A: Helen of Troy, You Know More Than, Darling, Guts, Leaving it Up to You, Fear, Gun--> Pablo Picasso, Cable Hogue
      Side B: Little Johnny Jewel, I Don't Care, Friction, Knockin' on Heaven's Door, Marquee Moon, Satisfaction (encore)
      Access CD available by appointment only. Please request parts 1 and 2.
    - Television-March 20th 75 Live at CBGB's/ Television Jan 17, 1975 at CBGB's, ID: 213.0216; 198480 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0216, Case 213.0216_pt.1, Case 213.0216_pt.2)
      Sides A and B: Venus de Milo, (I Belong To) the Blank Generation, Friction, (I Look At You and I set a) Double Exposure, Marquee Moon, Poor Circulation, Birds (Lloyd), Foxhole, Hard on Love (hard), Blank Generation (crossed out) Psychotic Reaction, Marquee Moon, Prove It, UFO, Poor Circulation, Double Exposure, Breakin' My Heart- (encore), Hard on Love (hard)
      Container Annotation: Tom Verlaine- Vocal, guitar; Richard Hell- Vocal, Bass; Richard Lloyd- Rhythm Guitar; Billy Fecca- Drums
    - Early Television - Summer '74 Max's/ Followed by Mother's 10/18/75, 1974-1975; ID: 213.0217; 198481 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0217, Case 213.0217_pt.1, Case 213.0217_pt.2)
      Side 1 (Television at Max's 1974): Psychotic Reaction, Excitement, Double Exposure, Venus de Milo, Fuck Rock 'n' Roll, Prove It, Change Your Channel, Fire Engine, Judy Said
      Side 2 (Television Live at Mothers 10/18/75): Marquee Moon, Friction, Torn Curtain, Breakin My Heart, Venus de Milo, Foxhole, Prove It, Poor Circulation, Little Johnny Jewel Pt III, Hard on Love (Soft)
      Format: 1/4 in. Audiocasssette
    - Television Live- CBGB December 30th 1976- Early Show, December 30, 1976; ID: 213.0218; 198482 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0218, Case 213.0218_pt.1, Case 213.0218_pt.2)
      Side 1: Fire Engine, Venus de Milo, Elevation, Little Johnny Jewel, I Don't Care, Friction, Marquee Moon
      Side B: See No Evil, Prove it, Adventure*, Poor Circulation*, Oh Me Amore*, Knockin on Heaven's Door (), Kingdom Come- *battery Failure, () Skipped
    - Television Live CBGB July 30th, 1976 w/ Talking Heads, July 30, 1976; ID: 213.0219; 198483 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0219)
      Side A: Fire Engine, Poor Circulation, Elevation, Venus de Milo, Foxhole, Knockin on Heaven's Door, Marquee Moon, See No Evil
      Side B: Prove it, Torn Curtain, Little Johnny Jewel, I Don't Care, Friction, Kingdom Come
      Container Annotation: MASTER, -P.D.-McKim-P.M.- Tom Verlaine - Vocal, Guitar; Richard Lloyd- Guitar, Backing Vocal; Billy Fecca - Drums; Fred Smith- Bass, Backing Vocal
    - Television June 10, 1978, My Father's Place, ID: 213.0220; 198484 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0220, Case 213.0220)
      Side A: The Dreams Dream (6:00), Glory (3:45), Careful (3:00), Friction (4:20), Little Johnny Jewel (12:00), Ain't That Nothing 6:50?, Foxhole 4:50,
      Side B: Knockin' on Heaven's Door, Marquee Moon cut
    - Television Jan 25th 1976/ Talking Heads- Recorded by Monte at CBGB - both sets, January 25, 1976; ID: 213.0221; 198756 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0221, Case 213.0221_pt.1, Case 213.0221_pt.2)
      Side A: Set I: Fire Engine, Venus de Milo, Little Johnny Jewel, A me Amore, Guiding Light, Marquee Moon. Set II: Prove It, Friction, Knockin' on Heaven's Door
      Side B: Torn Curtain, Let Me Out, Kingdom Come. TALKING HEADS: Artist's Only, First Week/Last Week..., I'm Not In Love, Building on Fire, [Track Unknown], Tentative Decisions. TELEVISION: Fire Engine
      Access CD available by appointment only. Please requests parts 1 and 2.
    - Television- My Father's Place 3-20-78, March 20, 1978; ID: 213.0222; 198757 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0222, Case 213.0222_pt.1, Case 213.0222_pt.2)
      Side A: Fire Engine, Prove It, Foxhole, Poor Circulation, I Don't Care, Ain't that Nothin', Satisfaction -->
      Side B: Little Johnny Jewel, I See No Evil, Elevation, Friction, Marquee Moon
    - The Sex Pistols- The Heyday- Fact .30. A Factory Records Documentary Cassette, October 1980; ID: 213.0223; 198758 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0223)
      Side A: Sid Vicious and Steve Jones. From interviews recorded during 1977 by Judy Vermorel
      Side B: Paul Cook, Johnny Rotten and Malcolm Maclaren's grandmother. Copyright on the interviews-Bondpen Publishing
    - Buzzcocks Sat Sept 1, '79 WPIX-FM, Irving Plaza, September 1, 1979; ID: 213.0224; 198759 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0224, Case 213.0224_pt.1, Case 213.0224_pt.2)
      Content: WPIX-FM 9-1- 79 11:11pm- 12:05am, Irving Plaza/WPIX-FM 9-2-79 8:40-9:10pm
    - [Jorma] March 24. 1981- Lone Star cont'd/ [Brian Brain]- Hurrah Thursday April 2, 1981, ID: 213.0225; 198760 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0225, Case 213.0225)
    - Bush Tetras, Pat Palladin CBGB March 2 1980, ID: 213.0226; 198761 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0226, Case 213.0226)
    - Chelsea ICA London Nov 1976/ Sex Pistols Nov 15, 1976 "Notre Dame" London/ Damned Studio, ID: 213.0227; 198762 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0227, Case 213.0227_pt.1, Case 213.0227_pt.2)
      Sides A and B: My Generation, Ready Steady Go, Anarchy, I Wanna Be Me, Seventeen, Pretty Vacant, No Feelings, Indian Summer, What Ya Gonna Do, Did You Do Wrong, Seventeen, Steppin Stone, Satellite, Problems, New York, Submission X/ See [yer] Tonight, Feel the Pain, I Fall
    - Tribute to the Stones July 24, 1978 Max's, ID: 213.0228; 198951 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0228, Case 213.0228_pt.1, Case 213.0228_pt.2)
      Side A: Live with Me, Used to Love Her, Wild Horses, Tumblin Dice, Play with Fire, Make Love to You*, Under my Thumb[], Brown Sugar[], Jumpin Jack[], Suzy Q(), Round and Round()
      Side B: Cocksucker Blues, Last Time, Route 66, Boppin The Blues, Chinese Rocks, Dizzy Miss Lizzy, Can't Keep My Eyes on You
      Container Annotation: Lloyd, Julian, Nolan, Thunders, Kaye*, Slyvain, Gordon(), Chance, Rath, Billy Balls[], Billy [Piano], Lyan Todd
    - Raincoats Hurrah May 14, 1980, ID: 213.0229; 198952 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0229, Case 213.0229)
    - DMZ/ The Jam CBGB Oct 16, 1977 (early), October 16, 1977; ID: 213.0230; 199069 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0230, Case 213.0230_pt.1, Case 213.0230_pt.2)
      Sides A and B: Boy From Nowhere, When I Get off, Destroyer, You're Gonna Miss Me, Out of Our, Raw Power/ Change My Address, Carnaby Street, Modern World, London Girl, All Around the World, Traffic
    - Clash March 7, '80 NYC Palladium, March 7, 1980; ID: 213.0231; 199070 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0231, Case 213.0231_pt.1, Case 213.0231_pt.2)
      Side A: Clash City Rockers, Brand New Cadillac, Safe European Home, Jimmy Jazz
    - B-52's- King Biscuit Flower Hour/ Clash - Cleveland Ohio, undated; ID: 213.0232; 199071 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0232, Case 213.0232)
      Side B: Safe European Homes, Stay Free, Police and Thieves, Julie
    - Clash, undated; ID: 213.0233; 199072 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0233, Case 213.0233_pt.1, Case 213.0233_pt.2)
      Sides A and B: -Capital Radio- London's Burning, 1977, USA, Pressure Drop, Hate & War/JR the DJ/Tim Buckley- Rebel, Culture -Dr./[N. Young], Men of Good Fortunes/Peter Hamill/ Boys Walls- Locks/ Blimp/ [Janitor of Luniar]
    - T.R.A.C. (Top Risk Action Company) Jan '84, January 1984; ID: 213.0234; 199073 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0234, Case 213.0234)
      Side A: Interaction, Nation N.B., Apprentice in the Crime Trade, DuCane Road, Fare Dodgers, The Bottom Line, Euroshima
      Side B: The Prolific, Winning, Gone to the Dogs, Ringmaster, Astroturf
    - MICK, undated; ID: 213.0235; 199074 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0235, Case 213.0235)
      Side A: The Bottom Line, Strike, Driven to Distraction, Sitting Pretty, Euroshima, Napoleon of Notting Hill
      Side B: Interaction, Takeaway, Strike (version), Under Starters, Orders (Bottom Line (version))
    - Clash Jan 5 '80 Friars, January 5, 1980; ID: 213.0236; 199075 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0236, Case 213.0236)
      Sides A and B: Clash City Rockers, Brand New Cadillac, Safe European Homes, Jilly Jazz, London Calling, Clamp Down, Guns of Brixton, White Man, Koka Kola, Wrong 'em Boyo, Stay Free, Jamie Jones, Garage Land, Armagedon Time, Police and Thieves, Aylesbury
    - Buzzcocks Irving Plaza 8/31/79 1:06-2:10 A.M./ Poet WPIX 9-1-79 8:02-8:38, 1979; ID: 213.0237; 199076 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0237, Case 213.0237_pt.1, Case 213.0237_pt.2)
      Sides A and B: I Don't Mind, What Do I Get?/ Orgasm Addict
    - NEW WAVE, undated; ID: 213.0238; 199077 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0238, Case 213.0238_pt.1, Case 213.0238_pt.2)
      Side A: Pistols- Anarchy in the UK; Clash- White Riot, 1977; T.V.- Johnny Jewel; Richard Hell- I Could Live with You in Another World; The Damned- Neat, Neat, Neat; Eater- Outside View, You; Stranglers- Grip; Snatch- Stanley I.R.T.; Lou Reed - Foggy Notion; Pistols- I Wanna Be Me
      Side B: Heartbreakers- Chinese Rock; Damned- New Rose; Lou Reed- I'm Sticking with You & Ferryboat Bill; The Seeds- Wild Blood; The Saints- Stranded, Buzzcocks- Breakdown, Times up, Boredom, Friends; Andrew Matheson & the Brats- I'm gonna be sick on you/ Generation X Live at Greenwich
    - Johnny Moped Monday Aug 7, 1978 Music Machine/ SLITS Aug '78, August 1978; ID: 213.0239; 199078 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0239, Case 213.0239_pt.1, Case 213.0239_pt.2)
      V.D. Boiler, No One, Save the Baby Seal, Make Trouble, Little Queenie, Darling, Bloomie- Oliver (?), Wee Wee, Something Else, Hard Lovin Man, Wild Breed, I Wanna Die, Incendiary Device
    - Echo & the Bunnymen/ Blitz March 31, '81, March 31, 1981; ID: 213.0240; 199079 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0240, Case 213.0240)
    - Petey D. 12. 04 Multinational Assoc., undated; ID: 213.0241; 199080 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0241, Case 213.0241)
      Sides And B: Bottom Line, The Max, Sudden Impact, Bad, The Washing Up, Strike, Hall of Flame
    - PETE, undated; ID: 213.0242; 199081 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0242, Case 213.0242_pt.1, Case 213.0242_pt.2)
      Content: To PETE. FROM Mick.
    - Clash Boston Harvard Sq. Feb 16, 1979, Pearl Harbor '79, February 16, 1979; ID: 213.0243; 199082 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0243, Case 213.0243)
      Side A: Bored with the USA, Guns On the Roof, Jail Guitar Doors, Drug Stabbin Time, Tommy Fun, City of the Dead Hate & War, Clash City Rockers, White Man, English Civil War, Safe European Home
      Side B: Stay Free, Police and Thieves, Capital Radio, Janie Jones, Garageland, Julie, Complete Control, London's Burnin', White Riot
    - NYC Clash Palladium Feb 17 '79/ Pearl Harbor '79, 1979; ID: 213.0244; 199083 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0244, Case 213.0244)
      Sides A and B: Jail Guitar, Tommy, City of Dead, Hate & War, Clash City, Safe European [Home], English Civil [War], Stay Free
    - Clash- Pearl Harbor '79 NYC/ Feb 17 '79 Palladium, February 17, 1979; ID: 213.0245; 199084 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0245, Case 213.0245)
      Sides A and B: Bored with the USA, Guns, Jail Guitar Doors, Tommy Gun, Hate & War, Clash City Rockers, White Man in…, Safe European Homes, English Civil War, Stay Free, Police & Thieves, Capital Radio, Janie Jones, Garage Land, Julie, Complete Control, Londons Burning, White Riot, What My Name?, Career Opportunities
    - Clash- Take the Fifth- Boston Sept 19th '79 Orpheum Theater, September 19, 1979; ID: 213.0246; 199085 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0246, Case 213.0246_pt.1, Case 213.0246_pt.2)
      Sides A and B: City of the Dead, [-----], White Man, Koke Adds Life, I Fought the Law, Safe European Homes, Jail Guitar Doors, Guns in Brixton, English Civil War, Clash City Rockers, Stay Free, Working for the Clamp Down, Police & Thieves, Capital Radio, [Track Unknown], Janie Jones, Garageland
    - Clash "Take the Fifth"- NYC Friday 21st WSHIT #2, undated; ID: 213.0247; 199086 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0247, Case 213.0247_pt.1, Case 213.0247_pt.2)
      Safe European Home, Bored with the USA, Complete Control, Hammersmith Palais, Koke Adds Life-->I Fought the Law, Jail Guitar Door, Guns In Brixton, English Civil War, Clash City Rocker, Stay Free, I'm Not Working For the Clamp Down, Police & Thieves, Capital Radio, Tommy Gun, Bill the Kid, Janie Jones Garage land, Armagideon Time, Career Opportunities, Whats My Name, White Riot
    - The Clash Live at the Coliseum 11/3/76, Subway Sect + Buzzcocks, November 3, 1976; ID: 213.0248; 199087 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0248, Case 213.0248_pt.1, Case 213.0248_pt.2)
      Side A: London's Burning, 1977, Remote Control, Hate & War, Bored w/ the USA, Deny, 48 Hours, What's My Name, Protex Blue Cheat, White Riot, Jamie Jones, Career Opportunities, Garageland
      Side B: Jamie Jones II (Clash). Subway Sect + Buzzcocks.
    - Clash and Buzzcocks Oct 26 1977, Edinburgh Scotland, October 26, 1977; ID: 213.0249; 199088 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0249, Case 213.0249_pt.1, Case 213.0249_pt.2)
      Side A: London's Burning, Complete Control, 1977, Jail Guitar Doors, Remote Control, Capital Radio, Hate & War, Police & Thieves, The Prisoner, Clash City Rockers, Bored with USA, Career Opportunities, Jamie Jones, Garageland, What's My Name, White Riot, White Man, Protex Blue, City of the Dead
      Side B: Boredom, You Tear Me Up, Can't Control Myself, Orgasm Addict, Friends of Mine, Drop in the Ocean, Breakdown, Love Battery, Times Up, Love Everybody, Boredom. Cloud's Club?
    - Clash April 1977 Edinburgh, ID: 213.0250; 199089 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0250, Case 213.0250)
      Sides A and B: London's Burning, 1977, Bored w/ USA, Pressure Drop, Hate & War, 48 Hours, Deny, Capital Radio, Cheat, Police & Thieves, Remote Control, Career Opportunities, Jamie Jones, What's My Name, White Riot, Garageland, 1977
    - Clash "Out on Parole" 24 July 78 Monday Music Machine, July 24, 1978; ID: 213.0251; 199090 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0251, Case 213.0251)
      Side A: Complete Control, Tommy Gun, Cheapskates, Jail Guitar Doors, Back Stabbing Time, Clash City Rockers, White Man, Capital Radio, Stay Free, Police & Thieves --> Blitz Bop
      Side B: English Civil War, Safe European Homes, What's My Name?, London's Burnin', Garageland, Bored w/ USA, Jamie Jones, White Riot
    - The Clash with Steve Jones July 25, Music Machine/ SLITS, July 25, 1978; ID: 213.0252; 199091 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0252, Case 213.0252)
      Side A: Complete Control, Tommy Gun, Cheapskates, Jail Guitar Door, Drug Stabbing Time, Clash City Rockers, Capital Radio, White Man, Stay Free, Police & Thieves--> Blitzkrieg Bop
      Side B: English Civil War, Safe Euro, What's My Name?, London's Burning, Garageland, Bored USA *, Janie Jones*, White Riot*, SLITS demos?.
      Container Annotation: *w/ Steve Jones.
    - Clash, July 26 Music Machine. Jones, [Shawn?], July 26, 1978; ID: 213.0253; 199092 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0253, Case 213.0253)
      Side A: Complete Control, Tommy Gun, Cheapskates, Jail Guitar Doors, Drug Stabbing Time, Clash City Rockers, What Man, Capital Radio, Complete Control
      Side B: Stay Free, Police & Thieves*, *Safe European Homes, What's My Name?, London's Burning, Garageland, *English Civil War, Janie Jones (cut)
      Format: 1.4 in. Audiocassette
    - Clash, July 27 1978, Music Machine w/ Jones, Cook, [Shawn?], ID: 213.0254; 199093 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0254, Case 213.0254)
      Side A: Complete Control 1, Complete Control 2, Tommy Gun, Cheapskates, Jail Guitar Door, Back Stabbing Time, Clash City Rockers, White Man, Capital Radio, Stay Free
      Side B: Police & Thieves, English Civil War, Safe European Homes, What's My Name?, London's Burnin, Garageland, Janie Jones, Bored w/ the USA, White Riot
    - Devo Nov 15th 1977, November 15, 1977; ID: 213.0255; 199094 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0255, Case 213.0255)
      Side A: Secret Agent, Jocko Homo (flick), Satisfaction, Too Much Paranoia, Praying Hands, Uncontrollable Urge, Mongoloid, Spud Boy
      Side B: Jocko Homo, Mongoloid, Uncontrollable Urge, Blockhead, Come Back Johnny, ClockOut, I Need a Chick, Jocko Homo
    - Devo- Max's 17 December 77, December 17, 1977; ID: 213.0256; 199095 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0256, Case 213.0256)
      Side A: Secret Agent Man, Pink Pussycat, Satisfaction, Too Much Paranoias, Praying Hands, Uncontrollable Urge, Mongoloid, Jocko Homo, Smart Patrol, Mr DNA, Gut Feeling, Sloppy, Clock Out
      Side B: Soo Bawlz, Pink Pussycat, Mongoloid, Gut Feeling (slap 'er), Sloppy, Wiggly World
    - Weirdos/ Dils, undated; ID: 213.0257; 199096 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0257, Case 213.0257)
      Side A: Weirdos (Negative Trend film at beg.)
      Side B: Dils - Class War, Give Me a Break
    - Dils, Hurrah June 18, 19th 1979, June 18-19, 1979; ID: 213.0258; 199097 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0258, Case 213.0258_pt.1, Case 213.0258_pt.2)
      Side A: Give Me a Break, Mr. Big, National Guard, Rain, Love House, Only the Lonely, I Hate the Rich, What Goes On
      Side B: National Guard, Mr. Big, Before the Law, Give Me a Break, Sound of the Rain, New (scratched out), New
    - Roxy Music March 8th 1976 Live at the Calderone, March 8, 1976; ID: 213.0259; 199098 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0259, Case 213.0259_pt.1, Case 213.0259_pt.2)
      Side A: Sentimental Fool, Thrill of it All, Love is the Drug, Mother of Pearl, Bittersweet, Out of the Blue, Whirlwind, Seabreeze
      Side B: Both Ends Burnin', For Your Pleasure, Diamond Head, Wild Weekend, The "In" Crowd, Do the Strand --> Editions of You --> Do the Strand, A Hard Rain Gonna Fall (encore)
      Container Annotation: B Ferry-vocals. A Mackay-Sax, oboe, organ. P Manzanera-guitar. Paul Thompson-drums. Rick Wills-Bass. E Jobson-promotion.
    - Roxy Music "Stranded" Tour, Nov 1974 Academy of Music, November 1974; ID: 213.0260; 199099 (Box 5, Media ID: 213.0260, Case 213.0260)